# FEDERICO VILLAGRAN

+34 662689581

www.federicovillagran.com

federico.villagran95@gmail.com

in

linkedin.com/in/federico-villagran



Madrid, España



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# SANTANA CAFÉ

Montevideo 2019 - 2022 www.santanacafe.uy

## Co - Fundador y Director

Leader and owner of specialty coffee shop. Responsible for collections and payments. Leadership and team training. Building links with potential brands. Communication in social networks. Company Accounting. Creation of new business ideas.

Today the company continues without my presence since I am looking for new challenges outside the country.

# PLATERO LEÑA

Montevideo 2018 - 2019 www.platero.com.uy

## Sales Manager

In charge of looking for new points of sale, supervision of sales, deliveries and collections. Responsible for positive after-sales relationship with customers

## **GENETICA TOTAL**

Montevideo 2017 - 2018 www.geneticatotal.com

#### Sales

Local manager. Public attention. Control of stock and imports.
Basic accounting control.

## **EDUCATION**

# **IRON HACK**

Madrid, Espana 2022

## **UX/UI Bootcamp Academy**

Tech academy focused on tech and design.
I seek to portray my creativity as an entrepreneur in the technology sector and enhance the UX area.

#### **ECONOMY CCEE**

Montevideo, Uruguay 2015 - 2020

#### Faculty

Completed 3 years out of 4. Focused on the area of accounting and business administration. At the beginning of the fourth year I decided to dedicate myself to my business Santana Café.

### STELLA MARIS

Montevideo, Uruguay 2007 - 2014

#### High School

Christian Irish College of Uruguay. Focused on the area of Economics. 5th and 6th International Baccalaureate (IB)

#### **ABOUT ME**

Passionate about learning and facing new challenges. I always seek to train and improve myself in the professional area as well as as a person. I consider the interpersonal bond within a company and when doing business to be very important. Businessman and entrepreneur with experience in business management, accounting, corporate finance and team

#### **SKILLS**

leadership.

- Team leadership
- Empathy
- People skills
- Proactivity

#### **PROGRAMS**

- Figma
- Google Analytics
- Myro
- Excell
- Hotjar
- Notion
- HTML / CSS

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish
- English
- Portuguese